Walid Bouladam

2 Tania Place, Blockhouse Bay, Auckland bouladam.walid86@gmail.com 0223664585

Career Objective

I am Graduate Systems Engineer with demonstrable experience providing both remote and onsite IT support services for Windows Workloads, on-premises and, in the cloud, leveraging both AWS and Azure technologies.

Some of the challenges I faced on a day-to-day basis include diagnosing and resolving desktop, software, hardware, user permissions, password resets, networking, printers, and scanners issues for individuals users.

In my downtime, I enjoy spending time with my partner by going on an outdoor adventure such as a hike, bicycle ride, or a visit to the local indoor rock climbing gym.

Skills Summary

Communication Skills

With over 10 years of experience within the Hospitality industry, I have been able to develop and refine my communication skills in order to collaborate, coach, lead and interact with different stakeholders. Most recently, I was exposed to Pair Programming and group-led projects during my time at Enspiral Dev Academy which helped me to further develop my communication skills in order to effectively collaborate with both my peers and tutors and be able to give and receive growth feedback.

Leadership

I have had many opportunities to lead teams of varying sizes during my time within the Hospitality industry. Recently, I led a team of 15 people as a Store Manager at Starbucks. Each opportunity has allowed me to continuously develop my understanding of what it means to be a "leader" and the necessary skill set to thrive and prosper as one.

Learning

I am a keen learner and have proven to be quick at learning and retaining new information. This is evidenced by my recent achievement of completing a 15-week, full-stack web development bootcamp at Enspiral Dev Academy, without any prior tech experience, as well as, recently securing a role as a Graduate Systems Engineer at Lancom Technology.

Experience

Lancom Technology

Graduate Systems Engineer • Auckland

03/2022 - Present

- Provide the first point of contact for client's IT Support through answering calls, attending to emails and tickets in ConnectWise and DeskDirector
- Troubleshooting and Resolution of issues involving individual users
- Complete new user and system setups
- · Assisting Senior Engineers and Customer Success Managers with client planning and communications as required
- Track and record time accurately spent on activities in Connectwise and DeskDirector to provide a technical audit trail for internal purposes
- · Acknowledge and follow ticket schedule as assigned by Service Coordinators or Service Delivery Manager

Firewood Pizza Haven

- Analyze workflow to incorporate quality controls and reduce errors
- Educate management on current costs and ways to reduce costs
- Evaluate and diagnose roles to make appropriate recommendations
- · Identify areas for improvement and make suggestions accordingly
- Manage operational changes, from suggestion through execution
- Recommend process improvements to increase efficiency

Starbucks

Supervisor • Auckland 09/2021 - 12/2021

- Monitor front and back of store/restaurant for operational efficiency
- Conduct inventory checks and restock supplies as needed
- Document and quickly resolve all customer satisfaction issues
- · Check register for cash and charge totals at the beginning and end of each shift
- Inspect store/restaurant for cleanliness and workflow efficiency

Starbucks

Store Manager • Auckland, Auckland

02/2021 - 09/2021

- Lead a team of store partners to create and sustain the Starbucks Experience for our customers and partners.
- Exercise discretion in managing the store's overall operation on a frequent basis.
- Supervising and directing partners, making personnel decisions (i.e., hiring, training, evaluating, disciplining, discharging, staffing, and scheduling), ensuring customer satisfaction and product quality, managing the store's financial performance, and managing the store's safety and security.

Education

Enspiral Dev Academy

Web Development • Auckland 12/2021

NZQA Level: Level 6 with 72 credits

Certificates

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner (CLF-C01), Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals (AZ-900)

Interests

Hiking

I see hiking as an important way for me to recharge my batteries from the hustle and bustle and reconnect with nature. A goal that I have is to complete all the Great Walks of New Zealand by the end of next year and complete the Te Araroa Trail in the near future.

Rock Climbing

I recently picked up rock climbing after watching the "Free Solo" and "Dawn Wall" documentaries and can't say that I regret it! I have set a small goal of getting my Lead Climbing license by the end of the year and big goal of climbing Aoraki/Mt. Cook within the next five years.

References

References available upon request.